PPT控制器（以下简称PPTController）和PPT控制器终端（以下简称PPTControllerHost）必须配套使用。您可以在微软的应用商店里下载到PPTController安装到您的Windows Phone 手机中，通过安装PPTControllerHost（http://112.124.49.118:8080/zh-CN/ppt-controller下载）在您想要控制的目标电脑上实现手机控制电脑的目的。我们提供三种手机和电脑的连接方式，由于网络环境，硬件，操作系统等的限定，这三种连接方式不一定在所有场合下都能正常工作，但可互补从而保证您的正常使用。

如果您是第一次使用本产品，强烈推荐阅读本产品的详细使用说明，
http://112.124.49.118:8080/zh-CN/ppt-controller/ppt-controller-feature-guidance-docx/ppt


PPTController and PPTControllerHost are client & Server app which must used together, you can download PPTController from Microsoft App store and PPTControllerHost from "http://112.124.49.118:8080/en-US/ppt-controller" which installed on your target computer for PPT presentation. Our app support three kinds of connection(Wifi, bluetooth, HotSpot) between Client & Host which ensure your usage under any unstable condition.

If you are the first time use our product, we are strong recommend you read the details operating documents
http://112.124.49.118:8080/en-US/ppt-controller/ppt-controller-feature-guidance-docx/ppt